(Stuart:)Oh, yeah. I guess it is hard.
(Howard:)So...
(Amy:)...where were we?
(Sheldon:)Well, I believe
(Sheldon:)we were kissing like
randy teenagers,
(Sheldon:)and your nose was
whistling ever so slightly.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Oh, don't be.
(Sheldon:)You were like a
foxy tea kettle.
(Amy:)Well, shall we start over?
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Amy:)What's wrong?
(Sheldon:)I'm not sure.
(Sheldon:)Earlier tonight, things
began organically,
(Sheldon:)and now it's
feeling forced,
like all the Pirates
of the Caribbean sequels.
(Amy:)Okay, that makes sense.
(Amy:)I mean, the mood's
a little different now.
We-we don't have to rush.
Oh, I know, but Leonard and
Penny think we're doing it,